

Professional Skills

Ferencz Balog

Junior Web Developer

Passion, Challenge-seeker, Professional improvement, are those three expressions that describe me.

In 2016 I accepted a job at a theater because of the passion of backstage activities and achieving new skills. Three years later I accepted the challenge to run a small enterprise alone from the passion of cycling and a few months later I started to improve my abilities as Sound Engineer and Web Developer.

Advanced

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, WordPress, JSON

Intermediate

JavaScript, API fetch, Relational Databases

Beginner

NodeJs, ReactJs

Still Learning

Java

■ balogferencz.artist@gmail.com

+40 752 813 860
Cluj-Napoca, Cluj, RO
ferenczbalog.github.io

github: FerenczBalog Linkedin: ferenczbalog

Work Experience

PUCK Puppet Theatre, Cluj-Napoca, 01.2017 - present Stage Technician

Earned soft skills:

Working under Pressure, Time Management, Attention to details, Communication, Engagement, Teamwork, Problem Solving

Spoken languages (CEFR scale)

C2: Hungarian, Romanian

C1: English

Balog I. Ferencz PFA, Cluj-Napoca, 07.2019 - present Founder, Food-Delivery, Stage Technician

Earned soft skills: Time Management, Attention to details, Communication

Passions

Cycling
Photography
Reading
Programming
Free-writing

Education

PLATFORMAIT.ro, 08.2020 - 08.2022

Hard skills:

Basics of HTML, CSS and JavaScript

TEACHBIT.ro, 08.2022 - present

Hard skills:

Advanced of HTML, CSS and JavaScript

My Projects

Mylifedash, 01.2023 - present

Hard skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API fetch

Because we live in a fast-paced world, I am working on a webpage that can help everyone manage their life. The first version of the website contains only a weather function, providing a three-day forecast fetching

RiderBox, 03.2023 - present

Hard skills:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JavaScript modules, OOP, JSON

While working in the theater as stage technician I missed a platform that can store the riders of current performances, so I created one. The first version was made using only HTML and CSS, the actual version is based on Javascript modules and Bootstrap.

The first web-portfolio, 2021

Hard skills: HTML. CSS

My first web portfolio was created with HTML and CSS, using layout technologies like flexbox and grid. The portfolio is a single page website organized in sections, writing about my passions, web development projects and about me. The webpage has an outer page, called blog, where I add additional information about my projects.